export const communityRules = [
    {
      question: 'Is this group the "IT Community of Uzbekistan"?',
      answer: 'No, this is a volunteers\' chat of "IT Community of Uzbekistan".',
    },
    {
      question: "Can I send IT-related posts to the UZ IT COMMUNITY chat?",
      answer:
        "Unfortunately, no. The chat is for volunteers and their communication. If the content you want to share is not directly affiliated with the \"IT Community of Uzbekistan\" or Shavkat Karimov(@pulsopros), it's best not to post it without Shavkat aka's permission.",
    },
    {
      question: "Can I post pictures from an event I visited?",
      answer:
        "First, ask yourself, is our community affiliated (or partnered) with this event? If no, it's better not to post it without Shavkat aka's permission. We have an open-source chat where you can post whatever you want (within ethical limits).",
    },
    {
      question: "Can I send an invitation to an event I'm organizing to the UZ IT COMMUNITY chat?",
      answer:
        "Unfortunately, no. Unless this event has IT Community of Uzbekistan as co-organizers or you have Shavkat aka's permission, we will not allow it to be posted in our chat.",
    },
    {
      question: "Can I post vacancies in my company, startup or hackathon team?",
      answer:
        "Unfortunately, no. You should either ask Shavkat aka's (@pulsopros) permission or your vacancy should be exclusive to our volunteers (e.g., an internship which only considers volunteers of IT Community of Uzbekistan).",
    },
    {
      question: "Can I add my friend to the group?",
      answer:
        "Unfortunately, no. Every member should be selected by the admins. You can ask your friend to message admins like Shavkat aka(@pulsopros) or other admins for the selection process.",
    },
    {
      question: 'Why shouldn\'t I just send "hello" or "how are you"?',
      answer: "Write everything you want to say in one message. For more information, visit aka.ms/nohello",
    },
    {
      question: "What is 2G community?",
      answer:
        "It started as a joke when Roman (@smart_proger_go) replied to an old message. The 2G Community is full of funâ€”we congratulate each other on long-past holidays, greet new members who joined ages ago, discuss past events, and embrace the slow vibe. Roman became the head of the 2G Community.",
    },
    {
      question: "Why is Roman the most humble and handsome person in the group?",
      answer:
        "He used to jokingly call himself so, and then everyone picked this up, and now he's known by everyone as the most handsome and humble person (as he always says).",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Keling Tanishaylik bot?",
      answer:
        "This is a bot for helping the volunteers to network with each other. Every week (sometimes once in 2-3 weeks) Shavkat aka(@pulsopros) launches the bot which matches a team of people together for networking.",
    },
    {
      question: "How can I participate in Keling Tanishaylik bot?",
      answer:
        '1) Vote "yes" in the Keling Tanishaylik poll in the group chat. 2) Press "start" in the bot and don\'t delete the chat with the bot.',
    },
    {
      question: "Can you congratulate people in the UZ IT COMMUNITY chat with birthdays or holidays?",
      answer:
        "Unfortunately, no. Because it floods the chat with identical messages, we are just too big now. But we have an open-source chat for that.",
    },
    {
      question: "Can you discuss anything related to politics, religion, private lives of people, etc?",
      answer: "Unfortunately, no. Keep it relevant to what we do as a team.",
    },
    {
      question: 'Does "IT Community of Uzbekistan" have rules?',
      answer: "Yes. We have official rules that are relevant to our work chat as well.",
    },
    {
      question: "My Telegram profile name and surname have to be real?",
      answer:
        'Yes. Your display name has to be in the "Firstname Lastname" format, not the other way around, in Latin letters and using default font.',
    },
    {
      question: "Do I have to have a username?",
      answer: "Yes. It is for easier communication. Username is important for tagging and mentioning.",
    },
    {
      question: 'What is "Bazaar Day"?',
      answer:
        'Every last Sunday of the month, we have "Bazaar Day" or "Shameless Self-Promotion Day", on this day, you can post your social media links, links to your private blogs etc.',
    },
  ]
  